Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 9, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Non-Contributory Group Life Insurance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 108)
- Box: 9, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Disability Wage Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 109)
- Box: 9, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Continuity of Service Rules, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 110)
- Box: 9, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Special Benefits Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 111)
- Box: 9, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Plan and Practices, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 112)
- Box: 9, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Thrift Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 113)
- Box: 9, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Wage Roll Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 9, Folder 114)
- Box: 9, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Educational Aid Program, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 115)
- Box: 9, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Continuity of Service Rules, 1958; Publication (Box 9, Folder 116)
- Box: 9, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan For Wage Roll Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 117)
- Box: 9, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Special Benefits Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 118)
- Box: 9, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Pension and Retirement Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 119)
- Box: 9, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Plan and Practices, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 120)
- Box: 9, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Non-Contributory Group Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 121)
- Box: 9, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Item 1: Continuity of Service Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 122)
- Box: 9, Folder: 123, Publication (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Plan and Practices, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 123)
- Box: 9, Folder: 124, Publication (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Item 1: Benefits, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 124)
- Box: 9, Folder: 125, Publication (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Item 1: Bulwark of Progress, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 125)
    Author: Crawford H. Greenwalt
- Box: 9, Folder: 126, Publication (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Item 1: A Tangible and Cherished Blessing, 1952; Publication (Box 9, Folder 126)
- Box: 9, Folder: 127, Publication (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 127)
- Box: 9, Folder: 128, Publication (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Item 1: The True Security, 1952; Publication (Box 9, Folder 128)
- Box: 9, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: Benefit Plans at Du Pont, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 129)
- Box: 9, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Industrial Strength- Assurance of Peace, 1952; Publication (Box 9, Folder 130)
- Box: 9, Folder: 131, Publication (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Item 1: Initiative in a Changing World, 1953; Publication (Box 9, Folder 131)
- Box: 9, Folder: 132, Publication (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Item 1: How Much Freedom or How Little, 1952; Publication (Box 9, Folder 132)
- Box: 9, Folder: 133, Publication (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Item 1: Business in Today's Society, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 133)
- Box: 9, Folder: 134, Publication (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Item 1: The Outlook For Du Pont, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 134)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Training, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Safety, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Company, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Esso Training Center, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Conference Leadership, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Replacement Table, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Box: 10, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Development Program Organization/Replacement Chart, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Box: 10, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Case Book, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Box: 10, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Leadership, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Box: 10, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Human Relations, 1954; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Box: 10, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Marketing In Training, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Box: 10, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Way To Work Together, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Box: 10, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Internal Communications, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Box: 10, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employee Forums, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Box: 10, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Training Film, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Author: John Bransby
- Box: 10, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the Historical Background of the ESSO Marketers, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Box: 10, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Organization and Operation of the ESSO Standard Oil Company, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Box: 10, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Advanced Industrial Sales Course, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Box: 10, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Basics of Supervision, 1955; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Box: 10, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Institute For Dealer Promotional Salesmen, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Box: 10, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Courses Available At Esso Training Center, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Box: 10, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Courses Available At Home Office, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Box: 10, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Petroleum Marketing In U.S.A., 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Box: 10, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Chart, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Box: 10, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Organization Manual, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Box: 10, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Management and Supervisory Training and Development: Courses and Programs, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Box: 10, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Information, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Box: 10, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Article: Is System Analysis For You?, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Box: 10, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Starting A New Decade, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Box: 10, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Manual, 1973; Publication (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Box: 10, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Termination Policy For Abolished Positions, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Box: 10, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Equitable Opportunities At A Glance, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Box: 10, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Actuarial Program, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Box: 10, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Box: 10, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Training and Development, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Box: 10, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Training and Development: Courses, Programs and Services, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Box: 10, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan: Policies and Procedures Manual, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Box: 10, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Group Benefit Program, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Box: 10, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Manual, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Box: 10, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Box: 10, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Management and Supervisory Development, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Box: 10, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Work Study Program, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Box: 10, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Insurance Education Guide, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Box: 10, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Box: 10, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Primary Organization, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Box: 10, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Job Enlargement, 1954; Publication (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Box: 10, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: International Management Seminar, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Box: 10, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Careers For Men At Equitable Life 1962-1963, Publication (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Box: 10, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration Manual, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Box: 10, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Annual Report (1959), 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Box: 10, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Manual, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Box: 10, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Public Affairs Policy, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Box: 10, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Administrative Training Program, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Box: 10, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Procedure For Administering the Policy Covering Absences Due To Transportation Emergencies, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Box: 10, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Discrimination In Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Box: 10, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: 1959 Vacation Policy, Publication (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Box: 10, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Box: 10, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Employment Application With History Record, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Box: 10, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Orientation Check List, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Box: 10, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Survey For Retired Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Box: 10, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Questionnaire, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Box: 10, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Box: 10, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Program For Employees Recalled To Active Military Duty Under Public Law 87-117, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Box: 10, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Active Military Service and Temporary Duty Training Program, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Box: 10, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Time Record Policy- Home Office, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Box: 10, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Insurance Education, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Box: 10, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Box: 10, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Personnel Activity Report, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Box: 10, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Box: 10, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Box: 10, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Actuarial Program, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Box: 10, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Box: 10, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Management Trainee Course, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Box: 10, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Group Benefit Plans, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Box: 10, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Personnel Department Working Plans For 1968, Publication (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Box: 10, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan Policies and Procedures Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Box: 10, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Box: 10, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Box: 10, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Information Releases, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Box: 10, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Lifeline: A Line To Save A Life, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 81)
- Box: 10, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Preparation For Retirement of Hourly Wage Employees in Niagara Falls, New York, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 82)
    Author: Woodrow W. Hunter
- Box: 10, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration Manual, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 83)
- Box: 10, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan Policies and Procedures Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Box: 10, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 85)
- Box: 10, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Rate Your Supervisor, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 86)
- Box: 10, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Personnel Administration, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 87)
- Box: 10, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Management Development Programs 1967-1968, Publication (Box 10, Folder 88)
- Box: 10, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Educational Programs (1961-1965), Publication (Box 10, Folder 89)
- Box: 10, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Summer Actuarial Program, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Box: 10, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Suggestions, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 91)
- Box: 10, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Suggestions, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Box: 10, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 93)
- Box: 10, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Safety And Health Materials, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 94)
- Box: 10, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: You and Your Hospital, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 95)
- Box: 10, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Management Research Creates Incentive Plan That Works, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 96)
- Box: 10, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Incentives In Manufacturing, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 97)
- Box: 10, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Incentives For Executives, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 98)
- Box: 10, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: The Rucker 'Share of Production' Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 99)
- Box: 10, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: The Rucker Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 100)
- Box: 10, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: EEI Management Development Survey, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 101)
- Box: 10, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Incentives In Manufacturing, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 102)
- Box: 10, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Wage and Management Associations, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 103)
- Box: 11, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Corporate Training and Development, 1957; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Box: 11, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Program, 1955; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Box: 11, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Box: 11, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Box: 11, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Box: 11, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Box: 11, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Box: 11, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Box: 11, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Non-Contributory Pension Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Box: 11, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Box: 11, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Assistance Program, 1977; Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Box: 11, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Box: 11, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: United States Business Performance Abroad, 1956; Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Box: 11, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Stock Purchase and Savings Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Box: 11, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A Handbook For Salaried Employees, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Box: 11, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Medical Expense Benefits Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Box: 11, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Plan: Improved Prescription Drug Benefits, 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Box: 11, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plan For Hourly Rated Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Box: 11, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Handbook For Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Box: 11, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Stock Purchase and Savings Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Box: 11, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Non-Skid Vol. 58 No. 11, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Box: 11, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Business and Economic Facts of Life For You, 1977; Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Box: 11, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Business and Economic Facts of Life For You, 1977; Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Box: 11, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Corporal Story, 1956; Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Box: 11, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Box: 11, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Safety Program of the Firestone Tire & Rubber Company, 1954; Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Box: 11, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Stock Purchase and Savings Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Box: 11, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits For Regular Full Time Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Box: 11, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1973; Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Box: 11, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Personnel Forms, 1951; Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Box: 11, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Skilled Trades Apprentice Readiness Training Program, 1957; Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Box: 11, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Handbook For Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Box: 11, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1961; Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Box: 11, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan For Non-Executive Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Box: 11, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: How Do We Select and Hire Employees?, 1957; Publication (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Box: 11, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Pensions, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Box: 11, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income & Life Insurance, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Box: 11, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Box: 11, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Insurance, 1970; Publication (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Box: 11, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Box: 11, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, 1970; Publication (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Box: 11, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1957; Publication (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Box: 11, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Coordinated Security For You And Your Family, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Box: 11, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Box: 11, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 11, Folder 46)